Hi, I'm Ann Myrick and today I'm going to show you how to get rid of what you don't want.
And that could be clothes, it could be toys that the children grew out of.
So, first, what you want to do is go through each room, each area, basements, attics, and look.
And you want to have pencil in hand with paper and you want to just make a list.
I would write down each room.
I would write down what you want to get rid of in that room.
And then how do you want to get rid of it?
Do you want to, there's probably going to be several different ways.
There's probably going to be a box or a sack for garbage.
There's probably going to be a box or a sack for Goodwill or Salvation Army or your favorite charity. Or there's also probably going to be a box or could be a box, if you want to make a little extra money, for a garage sale.
So the first thing you want to do is just go through and decide what you want to get rid of and a rule of thumb with clothes, if you haven't worn it in two years then you probably won't.
So you want to get rid of those.
If the children have outgrown them, toys, then you probably want to get rid of those.
Give them to a friend that has a younger child, whatever.
So you want to just go through each room and work with organizing, taking out.
Also remember to, like this is a great little piece that I store linens in.
But, and I have it alot of times I will shut it and use it for a little table.
What you want to do is if you have pieces like this, if you have things that have tops on them that you have stored in those containers you want to open them up and look in them.
Because there could be a full chest that I really want to get rid of but if I don't look in it I'm going to forget that I have these things.
So if I'm going to the trouble of having a garage sale or doing all this you really want to go through and pull out all the drawers, boxes, take the tops off and look to see what you have where you won't miss anything.
This is Ann Myrick and that is how to get rid of what you don't want.